Mason C.



mason.chen0087@gmail.com



+1 302 536 8999



linkedin.com/in/mason-chen0087

Summary

I am a blockchain and Javascript full stack developer with 10 years of rich experience.

I love coding and debugging. If my product is not like what I expected, I can't sleep on it.

My life guidance lies in "Prepare much and Win at a go".

My motto in development follows PP standards, which means perfectness and punctuality. I am a great blockchain and cryptocurrency enthusiast and a good problem solver at the same time.

Experience



🛜 Blockchain & Fullstack Developer

Self Employed

Jul 2020 - Present (2 years 4 months +)

- Maximally utilized Laravel, React, Node.js skillset to build industry standard web application
- Structured several internal systems comprising order entry/management tools, conversion/revenue reporting, and production workflow tracking, as well as design custom REST APIs built in Laravel PHP, and NodeJS
- Designed and implemented PHP web application, streamlining high-server traffic resource configuration and allocation



⟨ŏ⟩ Full Stack Engineer and Blockchain Developer

Braintrust

Nov 2021 - Present (1 year +)



📐 Blockchain Developer & Frontend Developer

BR Softech Pvt. Ltd.

Aug 2018 - Feb 2020 (1 year 7 months)

- Worked for 2 startups building company management & ad system
- Developed smart contracts in solidity and NFT websites



Frontend Developer

iExperto, Inc.

Jul 2016 - Feb 2019 (2 years 8 months)

- Utilized javascript technology in web development
- Kept working on PHP projects



🎵 Full Stack Engineer

Northcloud Inc.

May 2014 - Jun 2016 (2 years 2 months)

- Struggled to learn trendy web technologies.

- Analyzed business requirement to translate functional requirements into technical requirements and developed web application using PHP frameworks like Laravel, CI, Yii, Zend and so on.

Education

University of Toronto

Bachelor's degree, Computer Programming Apr 2010 - Mar 2014

Skills

```
React.js • Vue.js • Front-End Development • MERN Stack • MongoDB • JavaScript • SQL •
HTML • Node.js • Laravel
```